<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mingchen Jiang</title><link>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Mingchen Jiang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2008–2019, Steve Francia and the lee.so; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jiangmingchen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Paper Accepted]One Paper is Accepted by NeurIPS 2023!</title><link>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/post/neurips2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/post/neurips2023/</guid><description>Abstract Compositionality facilitates the comprehension of novel objects using acquired concepts and the maintenance of a knowledge pool. This is particularly crucial for continual learners to prevent catastrophic forgetting and enable compositionally forward transfer of knowledge. However, the existing state-of-the-art benchmarks inadequately evaluate the capability of compositional generalization, leaving an intriguing question unanswered. To comprehensively assess this capability, we introduce two vision benchmarks, namely Compositional GQA (CGQA) and Compositional OBJects365 (COBJ), along with a novel evaluation framework called Compositional Few-Shot Testing (CFST).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Email: jiangmingchen0129 [at] gmail [dot] com</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Mingchen Jiang Email: jiangmingchen0129 [at] gmail [dot] com
Research Interest: Machine Learning, Transfer Learning, Large Language Model
Education Background City University of Hong Kong 08/2022 - 10/2023
Master of Science
Major: Multimedia Information Technology Main Courses: Image Processing, Computer Vision, Complex Network, Data Mining, Cyber Security, Mobile APP Design GPA: 3.5/4.3 Dissertation: Domain Generalization in Image Classification (Supervisor: Haoliang Li Co-supervisor: Xiangyu Zhao) Northeastern University, China 08/2018 - 06/2022</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jiangmingchen.github.io/publications/</guid><description>Weiduo Liao, Ying Wei*, Mingchen Jiang, Qingfu Zhang*, Hisao Ishibuchi*. Does Continual Learning Meet Compositionality? New Benchmarks and An Evaluation Framework. In NeurIPS 2023 Track Datasets and Benchmarks.
Mingchen Jiang, Chunyu CAO, Jingyi Si, Dai Wang, Xingzhe Shi. Classification Method of EEG Based on Convolutional Neural Network. In China Computer &amp;amp; Communication. 2021 (22)</description></item></channel></rss>